Fiona and Zeke...
Kissed.
Like someone had died.
You're in love.
Where's your ring?
Oh no.
I love her.
How many times have you tried talking to Aemie?
I'm sorry, wife.
I never meant to.
She initiated the kiss.
You're staying here.
Why do you always have to get your way?
I said I don't want to!
I'm pregnant.
Ouch!
We haven't even...
The only guy I remember
Being with recently...
Was Moo.
Fucking asshole!
I'm gonna kill that bastard!
Did you know Aemie's pregnant?
I'll give you 10 minutes to explain.
Aemie! Aemie!
That's impossible, I second the motion!
Because...
Moo's gay!
I'm seriously the only sane one left here.
Aemie...
Tomorrow.
Huh?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
For now,
Get some rest.
Look at this.
Why tomorrow?
You can tell me now. I'm already here.
You can do it now.
Nah, don't get too excited, wife.
I'm already nervous just thinking about confessing.
Good night, wife.
Can you not, Louie Birkins?
Do you want the sun to never rise for you again?
Calm down girl, this is Shan.
Oh, why?
I just wanna ask something,
I feel like you could help
I can't help you with whatever it is that you're asking.
But this is about Aemie and her husband, Mr. Roswell.
About Cuz and Mr. Roswell?
Kaizer reached out to me asking for help.
You know what? Maybe we should just talk about it at school.
This will be quick
Later. You're going to school anyway, right?
- Alright, bye, see you. - Okay, bye.
Good morning, Momo.
Good morning, Auntie.
Ugh, it's still early!
What are you doing at our house?
Well, of course. I'm here to pick up my Momo.
Come on, let's go together.
Huh?
Oh, dear.
Niece, you're so noisy this early in the morning.
Go eat.
Oh, Louie, just help yourself.
Yes, Auntie.
I know your cooking is always delicious.
Hmm, really?
Well then, keep eating, okay?
I'm just preparing the food I'm selling later.
You know, Auntie, if I didn't have class,
I'd even help you sell.
Ass-kisser.
There's no such thing as excuses when someone truly wants to help.
Exactly.
Here.
Louie, sell my sticky rice cake to your classmates.
Twenty-five pesos per slice.
But we have a promo, okay?
Fifty pesos, buy one, take one.
Huh?
Auntie, are you really making me sell sticky rice cake?
Why are you complaining?
Auntie, I don't think he wants to.
He's complaining.
No, no, no, Momo.
Auntie, I don't think this is enough.
Maybe you have more back there.
Really?
Then,
Sell my tapsilog,
My longsilog, and my hotsilog.
Don't worry, they're packed in Styrofoam.
They won't be hard to carry.
Okay, Auntie.
That's fine.
Momo's coming with me to sell them anyway, right?
Oh no.
Come on, we're gonna be late.
Auntie, we're heading out.
I'm gonna be late.
There goes my niece.
Take care, okay?
Louie, take good care of my niece, okay?
Yes, Auntie.
I'll take good care of your most beautiful niece.
- Most beautiful? - Let's go.
I'm her only niece, obviously.
Move. You go first.
Bye!
- Bye, Auntie! - Bye, Auntie!
Yeah.
The boss already knows about Yaji.
But I didn't tell him about your dad.
If I tell him, then surely even you...
What?
Aemie's husband will kill me too?
Yeah, definitely.
But Aemie's my friend.
And...
I'm sure she wouldn't do that to Aemie's friend, right?
Mr. Roswell...
Killed Kaizer's parents,
Jerson's parents,
And Wallace's parents.
Those three are her friends, right?
Those three are his friends.
And you're just his wife's friend.
But, Vash.
What if they find out Aemie is Dad's real daughter?
How can we stop them from killing each other?
No.
It's safer if no one finds out.
But, what about Auntie Yana?
I mean,
I wanna know more about what happened to her.
Why does it feel like she doesn't know anything about what's happening?
Cai, let's just stay out of it.
You might end up getting hurt.
Alright. I have to go. Call you later.
No, you can't do this!
Alyana, I have to do this!
No!
I am...
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
I finally remembered my name.
But I still don't understand.
Why is my last name Ferrer when...
Miguel is my husband?
That's why I love you, babe.
I know, right?
Unless...
He's not really my husband.
Or maybe I'm a cheater?
Who is that man I keep seeing whenever my head starts to hurt?
And...
Why do I seem so rich?
And why are there so many shootouts?
I feel like the villain in an action movie!
Who?
Who is that girl I see?
Staring straight
Back at me.
I need to find out
Who I really am as
Alyana Heartily-Ferrer.
Before I tell Baby Ae and my niece.
Hi!
You're Aemie, right?
Can I sit here?
Oh, sure.
Wow.
You know me?
Mmm.
You're...
Me?
I'm your...
Guardian angel.
Oh my!
You're an angel?!
No wonder you're so beautiful.
Why did you come down to Earth?
Can I see your wings?
Where are your wings?
Can we be friends?
Of course! Seriously!
Why would I say no to being friends with a real angel?
I'm not literally an angel, but I'm your guardian angel—
Ma'am Aemie!
Jacob, come here, quick!
Hurry!
Oh no!
Huh?
Where did she go?
The angel?
Where'd she go?
Ma'am, who was that?
Oh, that was my guardian angel.
Why are you here?
Are you here to get a free meal from me?
Oh, you just missed Louie earlier!
There was so much sticky rice cake!
Hey, Jacob!
Hey!
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
Oh, it's Mr. Roswell.
He wants to talk to you.
Hi, Dong.
What on earth have you been up to?
Oh no!
Oh, sorry!
I forgot to charge my phone again.
Get ready later.
No. Just listen first.
That's not fair!
Why not just tell me now?
Yesterday you said tomorrow, and today is already "tomorrow."
I'll be the one to fetch you later.
So meet me at the gate. We'll go somewhere.
Really? Okay, okay.
Alright, alright, alright.
Aye, aye, Captain!
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
Oh, Jacob, your phone.
Hey, Jacob, your phone!
Oh, sorry, ma'am.
Thank you.
Ma'am, wasn't that girl pretty?
Here's the entire map of the Grand Park Hotel.
Your target is the hotel owner.
Alexander Park.
There will be a big transaction at around 9 in the evening.
So, we only have a few hours left to prepare.
Do we need a negotiator for that transaction?
No.
He's going to meet someone, and we don't care.
Our aim is Young here.
Finish off his target.
Nothing else.
Do we really need to go with Young?
Just so he can take out his target?
I mean,
This guy is old enough.
He can handle it.
Don't underestimate Alexander Park.
According to my sources,
There'll be a lot of guards at the location later.
The more, the merrier.
Our directive is to shoot on sight.
Anyone who tries to interfere with our mission gets a bullet to the head.
And you, Young...
You will focus on your target.
Any questions?
Nah.
I'm good.
Okay.
Good.
Let's get ready.
We need to be there as early as possible to survey the area.
And remember, keep your guard up.
We don't know who's going to be there until we get there.
Shit!
Are you ready?
How about you, babe? Are you ready?
I'm so ready.
Let's do this.
You're ready?
Let's go.
Grand Park Hotel.
This place is huge, huh?
Are you sure the meeting with Park is still happening tonight?
Of course.
He's meeting with the boss.
Once we're there, he won't have any choice but to talk to the boss.
If...
All they're gonna do is talk.
I hope not.
That's the part I'm looking forward to.
The...
Action.
Well, look who's finally here.
Why are you always off on your own?
Our starting five is never complete because of you.
I've just been busy.
Busy?
We're all in the same group.
How come
We're not that busy?
Just make sure you're not hiding anything.
So what's happening tonight?
Alexander Park, 43 years old.
A businessman, and an arms dealer.
He's smuggling the latest firearm models.
Arms dealing is Roswell territory.
Exactly.
That's why Mr. Roswell is meeting with him.
He's going to negotiate,
And if he refuses to cooperate...
Boom.
But did I hear that right? Ma'am Aemie is coming too?
That's what the boss said.
Why?
Hello?
Dong?
Where are you?
You're taking so long.
Oh no!
Huh? But...
I still have five minutes before dismissal.
I don't care!
Just go here in the entrance.
We need to go ASAP.
Oh!
My guardian angel!
Hi!
Who are you talking to?
My guardian angel.
How the hell can she be a guardian angel if you can see her?
Of course she only appears to me. She's my guardian angel.
Even Jacob couldn't see her earlier.
You know, she's really beautiful.
Next time, I'll ask her.
If she's willing to introduce herself to you.
Huh?
Why are you getting mad?
Do you want to become a guardian angel too?
The next time we meet,
I'll ask her if they're hiring.
Hmm?
You talk too much.
Just go here already.
I'll show you the real me.
Huh?
The real me?
Why?
Was the Zeke I married just a clone?
Oh no.
All this time?
All this time.
I've been talking to a clone every day.
Here, have some juice first.
Thank you, Auntie.
Amesyl should be on her way home.
I'm sure she's the reason you came here.
Because if it's Baby Ae, then, she's with her husband.
Actually, Auntie, I didn't come here for Amesyl.
I came for you.
Me?
Yes.
I just missed hanging out with you.
Really?
Then let's hang out.
What course did you take in college, Auntie?
What was it again?
I can't remember anymore.
What was my...
My course again?
Wait, why are you asking?
I'm just curious, Auntie.
How about Uncle Miguel?
Did you meet in college too?
Ah.
Hey, Caileigh.
What are you really doing here?
Why are you asking Auntie so many questions?
Girl, calm down.
I'm just curious.
Curious?
You know what, you better head home.
It's already getting late.
You're just giving Auntie a headache.
Oh, niece.
We're just hanging out.
It's okay, Auntie.
Amesyl's right.
I'll just head home.
Sorry for disturbing you.
- Alright, head home. - I'm really sorry.
Damn.
They're all dressed to kill.
But seriously, guys.
No matter how much you dress up,
You'll never outshine my good looks.
I'm so sorry.
Keep dreaming.
Yeah, yeah.
Lamperouge, that's a new one.
Wide awake, yet still dreaming.
Screw you guys.
Boss.
Hi, Kaizer.
Hi, Sebastian.
Hi, Jacob.
Oh...
You're...
Uhm, Vash, ma'am.
Vash Boulstridge.
Hello.
Mr. Roswell.
So you really are bringing Aemie?
Did I look like I was kidding, Lamperouge?
Things are getting worse.
She was receiving threats from the fucking Yaji.
We have to keep her close to keep her safe.
Got that?
Affirmative.
What are you whispering about?
None of your business.
Wow.
Wow, that's a lot of guns.
I knew it, you're a cop.
I'm not a cop.
A soldier?
Even less.
A bodyguard?
Close.
But no.
Then what are you?
A neighborhood watchman?
Good grief.
Ahh!
A traffic enforcer!
For someone this handsome?
No way.
Oh, and once again...
I'm the one getting picked on.
They're just jealous because I'm handsome.
What?
Nothing, boss.
Oh!
Are we watching a movie?
Is it a horror movie?
It's been so long since I last watched one.
Should we buy some popcorn first?
Just shut up and watch.
The location of the night mission is at Grand Park Hotel.
The building has a total of 25 floors,
Not counting the ground floor and three basement parking lot.
At the penthouse you will meet up with Alexander Park.
He will have a total of 17 bodyguards with him.
All armed with single semi automatic pistols.
At the vip room you will locate Roxanne Park,
Daughter of Alexander Park.
She will be an important part of the mission.
Jacob Lee and Vash Boulstridge , You are asigned to the security area.
There will be atleast four guards.
This movie is so boring.
It's all narration and graphics.
And...
Who are those people in the pictures?
Are those Parks famous?
Look at Kaizer. He's joking around, but...
He looks bored out of his mind.
Why do you always drag me into this?
Do you want me to cut you down, Lamperouge?
Huh?
There? Do we stay there?
It's always me, alright.
That's right.
Gear up and proceed to the parking lot.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Why are you dragging me?
Except you.
I still have something to tell you.
What?
Whatever you witness later,
Just don't freak out
And avoid making a scene.
Okay?
A scene?
Is there gonna be a movie later?
Is it a Viva Films movie?
No.
There's going to be a meeting.
An underground meeting.
Underground.
Oh! Wait,
I thought we were going to a hotel?
Oh, underneath it?
Who are you meeting?
Earthworms?
Underground creatures or something?
Ouch.
That hurts.
That's because your imagination keeps running wild.
What I mean by underground...
Is that...
It's going to be illegal.
Oh no.
Illegal?
You mean we're about to do something bad?
Oh no, Dong, what if the police catch us?
We'll end up in pris--
What if I throw you in jail for flicking me--
Ouch! Hey, that was hard!
That hurt!
I'm committed to doing this even if it's illegal.
Because it's my job.
You don't get it, do you?
That's why I'm just going to show you.
I know you.
It'll probably take ten years if I try explaining it to you
Before you understand.
So I'll just show you who I really am.
Hmm.
Oh.
He thinks I'm slow, huh?
Ouch.
Let's go.
Oh, wait.
Didn't you say there were two things?
You're just gonna show me one of them.
So what's the other one?
You sure talk a lot.
Come on, you still need to change.
Huh.
Why do I need to get dressed?
Does my husband think I'm naked?
What a pervert.
Pervert!
You're such a pervert.
Let's go.
Hello?
Do you recognize my voice?
Hmm?
Guardian angel?
Yes. I'm calling to warn you.
It's too dangerous.
There are three groups at the Grand Park Hotel.
Dangerous?
Why?
Hello?
What's she on about?
The food here is so good.
Hey!
Oh no!
Oh, what's going on?
They all look so scary.
Just relax, Aemie.
We're here with you.
I know.
Just look at my handsome face so you won't be scared.
You agree, don't you?
I'm handsome, right?
Mommy said lying is bad.
But if it's just a white lie...
Fine, fine. You're handsome.
Wait, why do you sound so unsure?
Didn't you notice—
Stop blabbering, Lamperouge.
Let's go.
Me again?
I always get dragged into this.
Why is it always me?
Oh no!
They look like wrestlers.
Hey!
What's going on?
Why do they all have guns?
Why--
Why don't I have a gun? That's so unfair.
One wrong move,
You're going to get your brain splattered all over this entrance.
It's Mr. Roswell.
Mr. Roswell,
Our apologies.
We didn't know it was you.
Please, come in.
Calm down.
I've been waiting for Mr. Roswell.
Are you Alexander Park?
Fuck!
We've got company!
Shit's about to go down.
It already did.
How much longer do you think they'll be?
Looks like we need to make our exit.
Let's go.
Let's split up.
Alexander Park is going to be on the top floor.
But we can't just charge in.
We need to be smart about this.
Copy?
Copy.
Let's go.
Put your gun down, miss.
I don't mind fighting women.
Shit!
That was just a warning shot.
Next time,
I'm aiming for your head, Meisha Lamperouge.
Fuck!
What are you doing here?
Dumbass!
You're disrupting our meeting.
I knew Mr. Park was your target.
My dad?
What are you going to do to him?
None of your business!
You know,
I could kill you both right here.
But I'm not, because I'm nice.
So you owe me your fucking lives.
So what now?
I'm going to give you the most unforgettable night of your life.
With your clothes still on?
You handle this, okay?
Also,
I saved my number in your phone.
Just in case you want to beg me not to tell Kaizer you're here.
Let's go.
Looks like you didn't bring enough men, Roswell.
Even if I'd come here alone,
It wouldn't have made any difference.
You should know that.
Now,
Let's make this quick.
I'm only going to give you two options.
First.
Sign this document.
If you do,
You have to stop interfering with my arms dealing business.
Do so,
And I'll let you live your life peacefully.
And the second choice?
I'll interfere with your business.
Hey!
You're a funny kid.
Are those real gold teeth?
Those look like the wrappers from chocolate coins.
I used to buy those too when I was a kid.
At the corner store.
Care to introduce the beautiful young lady with you, Roswell?
Perhaps, she's someone important to you, huh?
Why don't we speak with someone important to you instead?
Yo!
- Roxanne! - Am I late?
Dad!
Don't you dare hurt my daughter!
Oh no!
This old man's so judgmental.
Who said anything about hurting her?
Sebastian's actually really nice.
And Zeke's even nicer.
He just looks intimidating.
Guardian angel, where are we going?
There's too many of them.
I'll lure them away.
When I do, run.
Run the other way.
Here.
Oh no!
Pull the trigger if you have to.
Seriously?
Yes.
Now go.
Head to the lobby.
Once they leave.
I'm sure the Roswells will be there.
I'll handle things here.
Okay.
Go.
Hey!
What's going on?
Why are so many people dying?
Is this...
Is this what Zeke wanted to tell me?
Is this what he meant when he said this was his world?
Is this also...
Is this also the reason Dad died?
I hope Zeke's okay.
I hope, I hope he hasn't been shot!
I hope I don't run into anyone.
I hope I don't-
Oh no.
Whose mom is this?
I'm looking for sour soup seasoning.
Huh?
Zeke!
Aemie?
Aemie!
Lamperouge!
Where's Aemie?
I thought she was with you?
Fuck!
Dad?
Dad!
Zeke!
Moo?
Why do you have a gun?
Dammit, Aemie!
Where the hell have you been?
Why do you keep wandering off?
Huh?
Because, because of my guardian angel.
Your stupidity is going to get you killed!
Hey, wife!
I'm talking to you!
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Please.
Don't make me worry again.
I love you so much
That I won't be able to forgive myself
If something bad happened to you.
I love you so much
That I don't want you to know how fucked up my life really is.
And that's the goddamn reason why I'm about to lose my sanity.
Hey.
Please say something.
Hey!
Hey! Come on, let's go!
Is this really the time for a moment?!
Please.
Remind me to kill Lamperouge when we get out of here.
Aemie!
Ma'am Aemie!
Wife!
Boss, we have to go!
Bro.
That raid really wore me out.
Keep quiet. You might wake up Ma'am Aemie.
Was that all just a dream?
Did I fall asleep because of that boring movie earlier?
How was your sleep, wife?
It was okay.
But...
Zeke.
What really happened at the hotel earlier?
Why was there a war?
So it was real after all.
It wasn't planned.
I never meant to put your life in danger, wife.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You're sorry.
But...
But why did all that happen?
What is it that you really want me to know?
That...
That I'm a mafia boss.
Zeke, what even is this mafia?
Are they...
Are they just burglars?
Those scam syndicates? People like that?
Oops! Porn!
- What the fuck! - Shit, sorry!
No, boss. Mr. Roswell, wait!
Just wait!
Don't worry. See you, then.
Where have you been, Auntie?
I love you.
Hey, where'd you get that, Dong?
Where's your ring?
How's everyone?
What happened?
Doing good?
You look pissed.
What happened?
What if I can't bring myself to kill the last target?
Then you'll die.
And her.
And so will Aemie.
MkvDrama.net